Every once in a while, I have this dream.
It's always in Japan, in a classroom I've never been to.
I'm friends with everyone there...
And...
One of them is my very best friend.
That's the dream I have sometimes.
Wha... Huh?!
What the-
What? Huh?!
What...
Hold on, could this be...
That thing where you get summoned to another world?!
Etheric Connect-Crystal Ball, Crest-Invoke [Extrasensory Analysis].
It is, isn't it?! It really is!
All right!
Uncover what powers this otherworlder possesses.
No more jerks who look at me like I'm trash!
Mitsuki Mutou, age seventeen!
Watch as I take off towards a
bright future in this new world!
All right!
I have it. The Pure Concept this one possesses is...
Yes! Yes! Yeah!
Heave, ho!
Wait, what's going on?! You're just kicking me out?!
What the heck is this?!
Can you believe this?
They could've at least given me some money...
I'm starving.
That's right, I never got to eat breakfast.
I guess I'll have to steal something.
No, but if I get caught they'll contact my parents...
Oh jeez, I'm an idiot. I wish they'd contact them.
I wonder if there's a way to go back...
Probably not, huh?
Hey, you there.
Hey, are you listening?
Helloo? I'm talking to you, gloomy!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
You're a Lost One, aren't you?
Uh, "lost one"?
Yeah, you came from another world, didn't you?
What?
I knew right away from your clothes.
Oh.
And it looks to me like you're in need of money.
Uh... That's right...
Then you're in luck!
My name is Menou.
I'm a pure, just, and strong priestess.
So are you a priestess of some kind of religion?
That's right.
The church takes in Lost Ones as one of its duties.
If you're looking for help, I've got you covered!
Really?! Then I really need some money-
Maybe in your dreams, deadbeat.
"He who does not work, neither shall he eat."
If it's money you want,
you'll have to find a job and work for it.
But, you just said you had me covered.
Our churches are struggling to make ends meet,
especially the smaller ones.
But we can offer a roof over your head, at least.
Come along with me.
But really, I never imagined another
world would actually exist.
Are there, like, demon lords and heroes here?
Of course not.
Oh, I see! I get it now.
This is where I use knowledge from
home to make a name for myself!
What stuff do I know...?
Oh, what about mayonnaise?!
Ah yes, mayonnaise. It's pretty tasty.
You know what it is?
Lost Ones have been coming
to this world for a long time,
and much of their knowledge has been passed on to us.
That's why... Look.
Etheric Altar
Central Post Office
Wow, what is this?
Lost Ones always come from "Japan."
Over time, Japanese culture and language
got incorporated into this world.
Come to think of it,
we were totally talking Japanese and I didn't even notice.
What? You just realized that?
You're kidding me.
More importantly,
could you tell me what happened
when you were summoned?
Based on what you've told me,
it sounds like the one who summoned
you was the king of this nation of Grisarika.
Summoning otherworlders is taboo,
and yet those foolish Noblesse...
"Noblesse"?
Hmm? Oh!
Well, the people of this world are
categorized into three classes.
In the third class are the Commons:
The everyday people who
make up 90% of the population.
In the second class are the Noblesse:
The ones in charge of government.
That means the knights, nobility, and royalty...
...including King Grisarika.
He's king but he's in the second class?
That's right.
And in the first class are the Faust: those of the Church.
Like me, they serve the Lord.
We're also in charge of regulating
any Noblesse who violate a taboo.
Then are you going to arrest that king?
I'll report it to my superiors.
I'm busy with the noble mission of aiding people like you:
the penniless and homeless at the bottom of society.
I see.
So considering you're in charge
of a bottom-runger like me,
you must be on the bottom rung in this "Faust" class.
You shut your mouth.
Do you want me to abandon you here and now?
O Lady Menou,
I know you are great and noble at heart!
I beg you to have mercy on me!
As long as you know your place.
Well, you've got it right that I'm on
the bottom rung in this world, too.
Apparently, I have no powers.
They told me that, right after I got summoned.
They examined me with a crystal ball
and found out my power was null.
"Null"?
I bet the other one had some kind of amazing power.
"Other one"?
Yeah.
When they were going to kick
me out and I tried to get away,
I just happened to see her.
It looked like they summoned another one like me.
I couldn't see her face very well,
but even from afar, she had pretty big boobs.
Uh-huh. Big boobs are great.
Transmission
Oh, really? I'm on it, Menou.
There's no need to feel dejected.
I'm sure you have some incredible ability.
Oh, come on. You don't have to cheer me up.
Having no power makes total sense to me, actually.
I'm not trying to cheer you up.
Lost Ones always have some kind of power.
As far as I know, there have been no exceptions.
"Pure Concept."
That's what we call the powers otherworlders have.
"Pure Concept"...
That's right.
You definitely have some kind of special power.
For real?
For real.
Okay, we're here.
That's my church.
...For real?
For real...
Are you kidding? This place looks totally abandoned.
With no money,
we don't have enough hands to care for the place.
But you know, if your power turns out to be useful,
we might be able to make money out of it.
Wait, is that why you decided to help me?
Of course not!
I knew you were being too nice!
Anyway! Let's try and figure out what your power is.
Don't just give up. Come on.
Man, I don't know.
Look, just do it.
Link your consciousness with the power within you.
Try saying this out loud:
"Etheric Connect."
E-Etheric Connect.
Good. Now let your power flow into it.
Pure Concept
[Null]
Invoke
[Nullify]
I-it disappeared...?
Wow...
H-hey! Don't point that power this way!
I wouldn't do that!
But this really is amazing.
To think I'd ever have a power like this...
Oh, I get it now!
It's not that your power is null.
You possess the Pure Concept of Null.
So that's what that meant...
Null...
The power to nullify everything.
I get it.
Anything in my way, anyone I hate,
I can just get rid of them!
That's super powerful!
Come on, Menou!
Teach me what I might be able to do with this power-!
What...?
This can't be happening...
No way...
If I erase everything,
I should be able to change
this world to fit me...
I'm amazed that didn't kill you instantly.
But of course, you're a Lost One.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You're not to blame.
You've done nothing to deserve death.
I'm the villain for having murdered you,
and you're the victim.
But nonetheless...
The Lost Ones have brought far
too much harm to our world.
I'm a priestess: pure, just, and strong...
as well as an Executioner for exterminating Lost Ones.
Every once in a while, I have this dream.
It's always in Japan, in a school I've never been to.
I'm friends with everyone there,
and one of them...
is my very best friend.
Every once in a while, I have this dream.
It's different from my usual tedious life,
in a faraway world where I meet a precious someone.
Is this... that world from my dream?
Episode 1
The Executioner
I see.
So there were two otherworlders they summoned.
King Grisarika certainly seems to have
gone to great lengths with this scheme.
As soon as I confirm this information,
I shall make an attempt to infiltrate the castle.
What a hassle you have to deal with, Miss Menou.
Not at all. It's my duty, after all.
You should spend some time off there once you're done.
This is your first time back in your
homeland in ten years, isn't it?
Archbishop Orwell,
are you saying you remember me from back then?
How could I forget?
When that otherworlder went out of control,
it could have resulted in a calamity
equal to the Four Major Human Errors.
But at least I was able to save you, the lone survivor.
Yes. I couldn't be more grateful.
For allowing me to become a priestess, as well.
You have your Master, Flare, to thank for that.
I understand she trained you well.
She did.
Miss Menou...
I hope we can have a nice long chat sometime.
I'm honored.
I would love to, if opportunity ever allows.
Until next time, then.
Please excuse me.
I'm... so sorry!
Why? This isn't...
No, I didn't... White... The world...all white... I...
No, this isn't what... I just wanted... back to Japan...
White, hmm?
This certainly looks like blanching,
but something's different.
If this was the second coming of [White],
there wouldn't be any survivors.
Can't even die properly, I see.
You.
Move.
You're so half-baked it's pathetic.
Here I come!
You generated holy ground with a pseudo-church, eh?
You've always had a flair for flashy maneuvers...
Orwell you old hag.
You haven't changed a bit yourself, Flare.
You do love acting in secrecy.
My role is different from yours.
Besides, I don't think it was necessary for you to butt
in on this job of taking care of the otherworlder.
Leave it. I'm going to look around for survivors.
I'll leave that girl in your hands.
Huh? Isn't this kind of thing your job?
You recently became a Master, didn't you?
You should take on an unfamiliar task once in a while.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm a priestess: pure, just, and strong.
My homeland, huh?
My dear Menou!
Momo!
Ahhh, I finally got to meet up with you!
I can finally charge up on Menou energy!
Jeez, Momo. Let me go!
And stop wasting ether!
Demonstrating my love for you is never a waste!
Don't you know that whenever we're apart,
Hey!
I feel like my soul is ripped in two?!
As your first and foremost servant,
your Momo wishes she could stay
with you every moment of every hour,
every day of the year and never,
ever leave your side!
Ow!
You're not my "servant," you're my aide!
So, did you find out anything about the other Lost One?
Of course!
They're sheltering her in Grisarika's castle.
I totally figured out her location, too!
Of course you did. Good work, Momo.
But...
There's something I need you to do for the mission...
Uh... What's this?
It's the royal maid uniform!
It suits you so well!
Do we really need this?
It looks more elaborate than it needs to be, too.
Of course we do! It's crucial for going undercover!
Are you sure...?
But this disguise using etheric camouflage won't do.
I can't keep it under control.
All of Master Flare's inventions are like that.
You're the only one able to use it that well, as it is.
Momo?
Yes?
You just recorded an image of me in your scripture,
didn't you?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Hand over the page with the image! You always do this!
Rip out a page from scripture?
A pious follower like me could never do that!
Your reverence for our Lord has always been minimal,
even in your training days!
I don't care about the Lord.
Your image is the only thing sacred in my book!
There's five of them, I figure.
Don't tell me they caught on to your
investigation of the other Lost One?
I tortured one of the guards, just a bit.
Maybe that's why?
You really need to be more careful
about that kind of thing.
But fine, I'll take care of them.
Would you like me to help?
No need. Just back me up.
Stop hiding and show yourselves,
knights who serve King Grisarika!
Shut your mouth, Executioner.
You should have been satisfied
with the one you took out.
Now you're going to die because
you poked your nose in too far.
That's a pretty despicable tactic.
You summoned two at once,
intending for us to kill one of them.
Only so we can obtain a great power
to overthrow the Faust's tyrannical rule.
A trivial sacrifice!
I see. That makes things easy for me.
I feel no remorse killing corrupt Noblesse.
We'll be the ones killing you, arrogant dog of the Faust!
You little brat!
You go call for reinforcements!
Y-yes, sir!
Momo, one of them's getting away.
Okay, no problem.
Then how's this?!
Invoke
Flameblade
Did I get her?!
She blocked it?!
Etheric Connect-Scripture, 2:5-Invoke
[Thou shalt know that walls surrounding
pious sheep shall never crumble.]
Magecraft using scripture?!
She didn't even open her book!
That was too fast!
A dagger with a crest and ridiculously fast magecraft...
How is this possible?
Could you be the infamous Flare?!
That's impossible! She's too young!
Yes, she became a Master ages ago.
I'm Flare's successor.
A work of art that she created:
Her Flarette.
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
3:1-Invoke
[And the oncoming enemy
did hear the toll of the bell.]
No! Run for it!
Damn you!
Someone as strong as you...
Why would you... worship... some fool of a Lord...?
I'll pretend I didn't hear your blasphemous
remarks against our Lord.
The one you summoned was a monster
far worse than the likes of me,
but also just a kid,
far more ordinary than I could ever hope to be.
Momo, how are things on your end?
No problems here!
I took out the one that got away in no time at all.
Good work.
But still, we should hurry.
Please use this nightgown.
Thank you very much.
Um... Could I maybe take a quick walk outside...?
I don't have the power to authorize that.
Please make your request to a proper official tomorrow.
Uh, wait! Don't go yet-!
Excuse me.
I'm being held captive here, aren't I?
Another world, huh?
For some reason, I don't feel worried at all.
I just feel like something's misaligned,
ever since I got here.
Next Episode
The Lost One
Next episode: The Lost One.